<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="friend_eng">
        <item name="dialog_0">Sup, paul! We've not seen each other for a long time. How are u, what's new?</item>
        <item name="dialog_1">You write to much, wow...</item>
        <item name="dialog_3">Yes, better meet, i have a lot of free time so write where and when.</item>
        <item name="dialog_4">See ya)</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="player_eng">
        <item name="dialog_0">How am i? - I'm greate, thanks, btw near 5 years ago i've bought bitcoin and now i'm millionere, LOL!
            Now i live in center of Moscow, i've bought 2 flats - with two rooms at south-west and with three rooms close to the center. First apartment rent out for near 40 thousands rubles, i have lots of tenants, no matter this virus.
            Also i've got a new car, chevrole camarik, which you could saw in "Transformators", it's awesome XD, but i don't drive it much, bcs public transport in moscow is very advanced.
            I wake up at morning, go into a subway and ride to the work. Oh yes, almost forgot, now i have a job, almost a job, one my friend opened a company, and i help him with technical issues,
            and not only tecnical, at least payment is good) By the way last part from my bitcoin's money i put in a bank at a good interest rate, so i'm chilling, sometimes i think about stop helping my friend...
            But i help him not for money, i help him for process and results. Because you know, staying at home is boring, and sometimes you just want to go for a walk.
            I'm not boasting, as you might think, i'm just asking a question. And everything isn't very good, tax service always spams me, scammers always call me, i'm tired of it! But i'm ok)</item>
        <item name="dialog_1">And how are you, what's new? We've not chatted for 7 years, i almost forget how you look like XD (joke). But you know, we can meet one day, go to coffee shop or smth.
            Because i don't like chatting online, i like real conversations)</item>
        <item name="dialog_2">Wow< nice let's meet at 12 a.m. at friday 13 next week, at Arbat street from west side? There is a popular fast food point.</item>
        <item name="dialog_3">Nice, so goodbye)</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>